

PROFILE

Four years of professional experience. Energetic and adept at problem-solving, with a proactive and collaborative mindset, complemented by strong technical and analytical skills, as well as excellent communication abilities. Quick learner with a keen aptitude for anticipating challenges.

EDUCATION

Master Computer Network and IOT System

Conservatoire national des arts et métier (CNAM), Paris, France 2022-2024(Expected)

Courses: Al and ML (Libraries: Sklearn, PyTorch, Keras), Network Virtualization and Automation, Embedded Systems: Applications, Python, Internet of things **Project**: Network Data Analytics Function (NWDAF)

Bachelor of Computer Science

University of Science and Technology, Mazandaran, Iran 2014-2018

CONTACT

WEBSITE:

https://fatemehsalmani1.github.io/FatemehTheAnalyst.github.io/

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/fatemeh-salmani

EMAIL:

Salmanifatemeh1996@amail.com

REFERENCES

stefano.secci@cnam.fr University professor pedro.velloso@cnam.fr University professor

FATEMEH SALMANI

EXPERIENCE

DATA ANALYSIS INTERN LABORATOIRE D'INFORMATIQUE DU CNAM(CEDRIC), FRANCE

Jun 2023-Sep2023

(Libraries used: Pandas, Matplotlib, Tqdm, Math)

- Conducted data preprocessing and cleaning using SQL, Excel, and Google Cloud Platform (GCP)
- Performed geospatial data analysis with Python
- Executed proximity analysis and data visualization
- Provided quantitative data insights
- Contributed to optimization through data-driven decisionmaking

WEB DEVELOPER ROUZBAHAN COLLEGE, IRAN

2020-2022

- Developed and provided ongoing support for websites post-implementation
- Specialized in E-learning solutions, contributing to their development and management

WEB DESIGNER AND PROGRAMMER ADVERTISING AGENCIES OF IRANIANUK118, IRAN

2018-2020

- Produced efficient and elegant code using Python, SQL, JavaScript, CSS, and HTML
- Created motion graphics, short animations, and various graphic design assets using Adobe After Effects, Photoshop, and Illustrator

CERTIFICATE AND SKILLS

- Certificate: Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate
- Languages and Frameworks: Python, R, SQL, Julia, Assembly Language
- Data Visualization: Tableau, R (ggplot2, Plotly)
- Data Analysis Tools: Google Cloud Platform (GCP), Microsoft Excel
- Machine Learning Libraries: Sklearn, PyTorch, Keras
- Web: HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Network protocols: TCP/IP, UDP, DNS, http, SMTP
- Others: Adobe After Effect, Photoshop, Illustrator

LANGUAGE

English: Full professional proficiency

French: Level B1+ Persian: Native